我在躲Charles
I'm hiding from Charles.
我受不了他了
I can't take him anymore.
这里很安全
It's safe in here
他的踏板车上不了走廊的楼梯
'cause his scooter can't get up the steps in the hallway.
Gina 能不能有点同情心
Gina, have some compassion.
Boyle可是英勇负伤
Boyle got hurt doing something brave.
你又不用帮他做物理治疗 Amy
You didn't have to do physical therapy with him, Amy.
踩踩踩踩踩踩 推
Pedal, pedal, pedal, pedal, pedal, pedal, push.
Pedal, pedal, pedal, pedal, pedal, push.
美国公路自行车赛职业车手 罹患睾丸癌 切除右睾丸这脚踏车练习 让我觉得自己像兰斯阿姆斯特朗
All this cycling makes me feel like Lance Armstrong.
你是指服了兴奋剂
Like you use performance-enhancing drugs
而且只有一个蛋蛋吗
and have one teste?
就不告诉你
Wouldn't you like to know?
你能在这躲多久
How long can you possibly hide in here?
我把警监所有的电话都转接过来了
I sent all the Captain's calls here,
手机满电
my phone battery's at 100% charge,